Finding Aid for Anonymous Association of Suburban People officer’s papers, 1973-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gay/ Lesbian Buttons
  - Detroit and Michigan 1976-1993 (Box 1)
red cover: Universal Match, Detroit 'Become a Gold Coast Gent' crystal chandelier logo
black cover: Atlantis Match, Chicago crystal chandelier logo
Interchange, The 1501 Holden
black cover: Great Lakes Vending Co., Detroit 'I C'
yellow cover: Diamond Match Division, Detroit Schematic drawing of a freeway cloverleaf interchange (the bar located near the interchange of the Lodge and Ford Freeways); 'interchange' also symbolic of the voluntary exchange of power between dominant & submissive partners in a sexual relationship.
Menjo's 928 W. McNichols Rd. 48203
(2) white cover: Universal Match, Detroit books of 10 and 20
multicolored cover: Camel c. 2000 Atlas Match (Texas telephone area code)
One in Detroit (organization) 742 W. McNichols The Novelty Advertising Co., Ohio
Rhinoceros, The 265 Riopelle Diamond Match, New York matchbox 'fine food and drink' Drawing of the building with the Renaissance Center in the distance
Ron 313 861 6112 (personal name and Detroit telephone number) Universal Match, St. Louis
Tiffany's 17436 Woodward Tiffany Enterprises, Troy, MI
black cover: Universal Match, Detroit/ 'The Aristocrat' Universal Match, St. Louis
red cover: '12 inch weenies and hot buns' Inside cover: 'Tiffany's Trick Book/ U.S.D.A. Prime'
Other Michigan, Ontario Gay Bars, Restaurants, Resorts [Included in Folder 31]
Pontiac
Poppers' Pontiac 55 Glenwood 48058 Universal Match Corp., St. Louis matchbox of 14 matches 'PP' 'Men's Night Sun., Well Drinks 9-1, 75c/ Wed Beer Bust, Draft Beer 50c' 'in the Glenwood Plaza'
Windsor, Ontario
Happy Tap, Club 1056 Wyandotte SE Kaeser & Blair Inc., Cincinnati 'Exotic Nude Male Dancers' with photograph of five dancers in posing straps on the lower level of the club
Flint
Downtowners Club, The 510 S. Saginaw St. Raffoul Advertising Specialists, Flint
Saugatuck/ Douglas
Douglas Dunes/ Sir Douglas 333 Blue Star Highway, Douglas Shedd-Brown, Inc., Minneapolis 'Just minutes from beautiful Lake Michigan' 'Sir Douglas casually elegant dining & drinks'
Jocko's Blue Star Highway, Saugatuck Atlantis Match Co., Chicago 'Cocktails, Restaurant, Motel'
Miscellaneous
Sexual Outlaw, The by John Rechy Lion Match Corp. of America, New York 'Now a Dell Paperback!' 'The Grove Press Bestseller Now a Dell Book $2.25'
I know he's pretty BUT CAN HE TYPE? Superior Match Co., Chicago Equality Products, Louisville, KY
Liberated Men Are Better Superior Match Co., Chicago
Other American, Canadian Gay Bars, Restaurants, Businesses [Folder 32]
Toronto
Barn, The/ Les Cavaliers 418 Church St./ 83 Granby St. Tom of Finland drawing on cover, drawing of Les Cavaliers building on back cover.
Buddy's 370 Church St.
Dudes 10 Breadalbane 'the best bar none.' Photograph of male with Levis open at top of fly.
Cavaliers, Les/ Jo Jo's Licensed 418 Church St./ 83 Granby St. Drawing of Les Cavaliers building on back cover.
Lovecraft 108 Yorkville Ave. 'Dedicated to the art of love' 'Mail Order Catalogue $1.00'
Chicago
Gold Coast, The 501 N. Clark 60610 Etienne/ Stephen drawing on cover.
Male Hide Leathers, Inc. 66 W. Illinois 60610
Pub, Le/ Alfie's 1944 N. Clark St. 60614/ 900 N. Rush St.
New York City
Saint, The
Spike, The 120 Eleventh Ave. Railroad spike as letter 'i' in Spike.
Uncle Charlie's Restaurant 544 Third Ave. 'UCR' logo with male symbol forming a portion of the letter 'R.'
Washington, D.C.
Eagle, D.C./ Eagle in Exile 904 Ninth St., N.W./ 953 Ninth St., N.W. 'If You're Man Enough.' Leatherman and eagle logo.
Lost & Found 56 'L' St., S.E. Washington traffic circle with directional arrows logo. 'Dinner Reservations'
Saint Louis
Clementine's 2001 Menard 63104 'Home of The Spirit of St. Louis' Hand gun, target & leatherman logo.
San Francisco
Eagle, S.F. 398 Twelfth St. Head of eagle logo.
Seattle
Mr. Larry's 801 Pike buck in the woods logo 'Happy hunting!' 'restaurant & bar'
Unknown Origin
Velvet Turtle, The Diamond Match Div., Los Angeles Turtle in top hat, bow tie & monocle logo. matchbox
Series X Gay/ Lesbian Buttons 1980-1999 [Folder 33]
Gay General (3 on card)
Have a very Gay Christmas c. 1982
Gay/ Lesbian Marches on Washington & Political (3 on card)
Gay Vote 1980, National March on Washington 1993
HIV/ AIDS-Related (3 on card)
Red ribbon, 'All I Want is the cure and my friends back,' 'Play Safe! Wellness Network'
National Gay/ Lesbian Organizations (3 on card, 1 loose military i.d. tags)
National Gay Task Force, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force 1999, Human Rights Campaign Fund (Operation Lift the Ban dog tags)
Pink Triangles & Related (Nazi concentration camp symbol for homosexuals) (4 on card)
'No More Shit! Toronto 1981'
Series XI Detroit/ Michigan Gay/ Lesbian Buttons & 1 Bookmark 1976-1993 [Folder 34]
Association of Suburban People (ASP) Metro Detroit, card #1 (3 on card) ca. 1976-77 and 1980-81
Association of Suburban People (ASP) Metro Detroit, card #2 (1 on card)
ASP members/ officers Bill Thompson, Frank Martin 50th Birthday Bash 1988
Metro Detroit Gay/ Lesbian Organizations card #1 Michigan Organization for Human Rights (MOHR) (2 on card)
one c. 1979
Metro Detroit Gay/ Lesbian Organizations card #2 (3 on card)
Detroit Area Gay/ Lesbian Council G/L Pride Festival 1984; (probably) Triangle Foundation, Detroit
MI L/G Pride Parade 1986 and MI Delegation, March on Washington 1993 (3 on card)
Metro Detroit Gay Businesses (3 on card, 1 loose bookmark)
Chosen Books, probably Detroit & Chosen Books/ METRA, probably Royal Oak 1984; Backstage Dinner Theatre, probably 17630 Woodward, Detroit ca. 1981-1993; Chosen Books bookmark, Royal Oak ca. 1983-2007 (dates store located in Royal Oak)
Detroit Gay Leather Clubs, The Interchange Bar (1501 Holden) (3 on card)
Selectmen 1978; Tribe 1981; Studs-30/ Interchange 'Jailhouse Rock 1985'
Magnum P. I./ Tom Selleck (1 on card) c. 1980 (Thomas W. Selleck b. Jan 29, 1945 Detroit)
Related Material
The papers of ASP president Daniel R. Sivil (0167 Aa 2) and Douglas M. Haller (2011138 Aa 2, Ac) contain files relating to the history of ASP. The organization's newsletters are cataloged separately in the Bentley collection (EA 186 A838 N558).